<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors on Do you still need a Third Testament?</title>
    <link>/en/authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Authors on Do you still need a Third Testament?</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>pt-br</language>
    <copyright>Written in 2018 by Daniella Mesquita (https://danimesq.eth.link)</copyright>
    
        <atom:link href="/en/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2nd letter to the Blumenauans</title>
      <link>/en/2019/06/2nd-letter-to-the-blumenauans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 14:33:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/2019/06/2nd-letter-to-the-blumenauans/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../../img/letters/blumenauans/2.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-1&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1.) You do not know when this was written, nor who writes, but know who wants to talk to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(2.) I do not know if you are a man or a woman.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(3.) But what does it matter? You are reading, and you can build with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(4.) I do not know your mistakes, your name, your surname, your schooling, your financial conditions;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(5.) However, I direct this letter to any resident of Blumenau and neighboring towns, who may receive light by reading this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(6.) Daniell, a very flawed servant, I write this after contending and inclining to desires.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(7.) I saw a wind like never before in Blumenau, dragging leaves and making a loud sound.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(8.) I had thought of throwing this letter from a high place, but I was told that this is not necessary, and I have to write the letters without thinking of other things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-2&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 2&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1.) I am perplexed about today&amp;rsquo;s Christianity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(2.) Only talk about prosperity, victory, achievements, a fabulous life gifted, superb, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(3.) They teach people to be like the foolish;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(4.) Of whom the Bible briefly referred, as also predicted what is happening today, in 2 Timothy 4: 3:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(5.) &amp;ldquo;For the time will come when they will not endure sound doctrine, but with their ears itching, they will heap doctors for themselves according to their own lusts.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(6.) Who are these doctors? Pastors who preach prosperity today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(7.) And many churches do not want to admit losing believers to other churches&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(8.) (competitors, as if it were a capital competition) and then they preach only what pleases man, and so they fill their churches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(9.) But we can not speak pleasing man, but speaking what is fitting for building up people and souls to please God.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(10.) 1 Corinthians 4:14: &amp;ldquo;I do not write these things to put you to shame, but I admonish you as my beloved children.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(11.) If I have a son that hinders him;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(12.) I will allow him to do this within my house so that while he, alive, does not come out of it,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(13.) Or with love will I rebuke him, lest he come out dead?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(14.) It is similar to that which happens in the churches today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(15.) Do they prefer that the faithful keep their souls dying, or that they hear the truth even if they want to leave?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(16.) What&amp;rsquo;s the use of having the church full of lost souls?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(17.) For the church with only seven saved members is better than a church with a thousand confused members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(18.) As it is written, many shall be called, but few shall be chosen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(19.) And: the door is narrow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(20.) Galatians 1: 9-10: &amp;ldquo;Now as I told you again, now I say unto you again, If any man shall preach any other gospel unto you than that which ye have received, let it be appart: for I persuade men now or to God? Or do I seek to please men? If I were still pleasing men, I would not be a servant of Christ. &amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-3&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 3&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1.) Today is taught to crucify, not to carry the cross.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(2.) Now, to have glory in heaven, must we have glory on earth?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(3.) Is God unjust because the wicked are glorified on earth while the good suffer?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(4.) Do Christians have to live as kings on earth?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(5.) Has Christ ever returned, and here is paradise?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(6.) Is here on earth heaven for the wicked and hell for the good?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(7.) But the earth is not everything, and it is not here that it will be revealed to us what we are to be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(8.) For Earth, hell and heavens are similar, but different.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(9.) 1 Corinthians 15:19: &amp;ldquo;If we hope in Christ alone in this life, we are the most miserable of all men.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(10.) For the one who, knowing Christ, sins; than he who sins in his ignorance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(11.) By those who say they love Christ, but their hearts are on the earth,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(12.) And they give priority to things that are vanity (vanity are things that are not eternal), they are like the most sinful of all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-4&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 4&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1.) Who sins more? The wanderer who can become a new creature, or what he says is a new creature and does not recognize his mistakes?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(2.) For whoever claims to be already converted, and sinning voluntarily,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(3.) He does not allow himself to become Spirit and truth, not word.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(4.) Can he who says he has become converted convert himself without believing to have deviated from the path?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(5.) For they live as deviants but claiming to be converted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(6.) And yet they want to repress whom they call sinners!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(7.) What will we do about people like that? Teach them, admonishing with humility that comes from love,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(8.) And fight in prayers for those whom we believe may come to repentance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(9.) As for us, let us not think that God and the Bible are equal to these hypocrites, their doctrines, and their churches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(10.) Let us love above all things, loving God above all things,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(11.) Loving the neighbor more than we love, and loving us above the corruptions that this world offers;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(12.) Gluttonies, drunking, smoking, sensuality, malice, envy and things similar to these.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(13.) For these are evil to the body (the temple of the Holy Spirit) and to the soul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(14.) I am neither a priest nor a pastor. I do not consider myself a worker, because of so many failures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(15.) I have no church, I have no religion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(16.) But I ask that you receive this letter as receiving it from an apostle, knowing that I am not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(17.) May our greatest love be to Christ Jesus, so also shall we love the Father; for God is one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(18.) And if we love Jesus, we suffer with him, and with him we shall rise in glory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(19.) Galatians 1: 7: &amp;ldquo;Who is no other, but there are some who trouble you and want to disrupt the gospel of Christ.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(20.) Today, many churches are uneasy and scandalized;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(21.) Being hypocrites on one side, disbelieving on the other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-5&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 5&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1.) But he who is of God knows that in himself he receives the presence of Jesus and the Spirit,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(2.) Who loves his neighbor and helps all, who seek to gather with other sincere Christians and admonish the wicked,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(3.) Who seeks knowledge of the truth and is not embarrassed by the affairs of this life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(4.) Colossians 3:23: &amp;ldquo;Whatever you do, do it with all your heart, as to the Lord, and not to men.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(5.) John 12: 42-43: &amp;ldquo;Yet many of the rulers believed in him;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(6.) But they did not confess him because of the Pharisees, lest they be expelled from the synagogue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(7.) For they loved the glory of men more than the glory of God. &amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(8.) Matthew 24:35: &amp;ldquo;Heaven and earth shall pass away, but my words shall not pass away.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(9.) Matthew 24: 38-39: &amp;ldquo;For as in the days before the flood they did eat, drink, marry, and marry, until the day that Noah entered into the ark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(10.) And they did not perceive it, until the flood came, and brought them all, so shall also the coming of the Son of man be. &amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(11.) And why do those who say they are converted but sinners sin?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(12.) John 9: 39-41: &amp;ldquo;And Jesus said unto him,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(13.) I have come into this world for judgment, that those who do not see may see, and those who see may be blind. &amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(14.) And the Pharisees that were with him heard it, and said unto him,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(15.) Are we also blind? Jesus said to them,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(16.) If ye were blind, ye would have no sin; but as you now say, we see; therefore your sin remains. &amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(17.) Galatians 5:14: &amp;ldquo;Let the whole law be fulfilled in one word, in this: thou shalt love thy neighbor as thyself.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(18.) Romans 6:12: &amp;ldquo;Let not sin therefore reign in your mortal body, that ye should obey it in its lusts.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(19.) 2 Corinthians 2:17: &amp;ldquo;For we are not as many as counterfeiters of the word of God, but we speak of Christ sincerely, as of God in the presence of God.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(20.) Read also Galatians 5: 17-25, and Philippians 4.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(21.) As a man, I got very tired writing this letter, but my spirit rejoices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(22.) Read with love and diligence all the biblical quotations contained herein.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(23.) Grace and peace, and love, be with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(24.) &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:mssdaniellmesquita@gmail.com&#34;&gt;mssdaniellmesquita@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(25.) Blumenau, 03/15/18&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3rd letter to the Blumenauans</title>
      <link>/en/2019/06/3rd-letter-to-the-blumenauans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 14:33:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/2019/06/3rd-letter-to-the-blumenauans/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../../img/letters/blumenauans/3.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-1&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1.) Written letter of outburst to edify, so that I may absorb what is written here and gain experience;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(2.) And that other people may be comforted to know that I, Daniell, have been suffering with the same weaknesses of the flesh to which all people are subject.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(3.) My feelings are now anger, a spirit of strife, doubt, sorrow, rancor, fear, greed, and the like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(4.) I do not settle for foolishness, and that makes me angry when this foolishness comes from my own mother.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(5.) By the Bible, I must obey her in everything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(6.) Even to write this I will go, for I write under the table so that the servants of Satan do not spy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(7.) And in this I feel greed for material things:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(8.) With Bitcoin, I would have given my mother money for rent and freight;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(9.) And having some items I could cover the table to be able to write without tiring myself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-2&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 2&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1.) And I am already tired: in body, mind and spirit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(2.) So tired that sometimes I can not even write (and describe) everything I feel in anguish in these tribulations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(3.) I can not fall after confessing Christ, but when I see I am disobeying the Holy Bible of God.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(4.) And that two months ago did not happen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(5.) The foolishness of my mother has impaired my flesh and scandalized me, for I am perplexed by what she has done while the devil tempts her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(6.) She being willing before to eat certain foods, preventing me from speaking and handling,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(7.) Keeping me from accessing the Internet, not wanting to call her daughter to receive her money, being able to leave here without paying rent and leaving our things in the house.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(8.) And staying quiet with nervous breakdown thinking about bad things or talking too much,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(9.) And doing things that hurt us when we know that there are malicious men filming wanting to twist our words and deeds; all this has made me distressed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(10.) And even more distressed I feel in knowing that I am sinning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(11.) I feel like crap; like a little clown toy in the hands of a god.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(12.) I want to die, and how I wish I had the courage to do it myself!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(13.) How I have done the will of the devil and his devils!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(14.) And wrathful to me who doeth this more than I, I have opened yet more spiritual doors unto them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(15.) Is it because I want to sin or are joking with me?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(16.) Is there anyone making me sin so that I am afraid?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(17.) Is it a grace to serve God out of fear?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(18.) Is it good to subject ourselves to Satan in his &amp;ldquo;do not taste, do not touch, do not handle&amp;rdquo;?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(19.) Am I not extinguishing the Spirit when I am gone?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(20.) Fill my spiritual emptiness with the words and deeds of Satan or God?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(21.) Is my mother bad or am I the one who can not speak with more love?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-3&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 3&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1.) When we fear or irritate ourselves, love is not properly present.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(2.) When we become distracted by something of this world, we open doors for demons to command us what to say and what to do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(3.) Again, I repeat: when we have any negative feelings, the devil and demons command us and so we do and we speak what they want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(4.) And they do it through the flesh, the same that is corrupted on the earth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(5.) But the Spirit is kind, eternal, and incorruptible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(6.) Now the devil wants our corruption;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(7.) Therefore he tempts us to bow down to the flesh, and when inclined to the flesh he commands us to do things that are not convenient.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(8.) Are we, therefore, being free and doing our will?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(9.) The will is a feeling, just as love is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(10.) There is love that is not love, but our will, in fact, is never will.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(11.) The only thing in our being to feel desire, namely, is our soul;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(12.) Who only wants to live in Spirit and in truth, and to be saved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(13.) In any case, we live in servitude, serving the flesh by &amp;ldquo;freedom&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;will,&amp;rdquo; or by serving the Spirit out of fear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(14.) Now in the flesh, liberty and will are false, so that these things are found only in soul and love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(15.) For what? For love, will we sin and serve the flesh by loving God and believing that he forgives this and that we will be converted at an older age?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(16.) Not at all; for true and complete love begins by: loving God above all things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(17.) If we love God, we are not afraid of him; but we do not want to grieve for ourselves and/or ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(18.) But with the new testament of our Lord Jesus Christ, we understand this even more grandly, as the first commandment:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(19.) Thou shalt love thy neighbor as thyself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(20.) Then we will love ourselves and our neighbor alike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(21.) And if we love our neighbor, we love ourselves;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(22.) For one who does not love can not love, and one who does not understand can not understand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(23.) Indeed, if we love one another (as Christ has loved us), we also love our souls.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(24.) And if we love our souls, we will do his will, which is to live in the Spirit and in truth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-4&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 4&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1.) I stopped what I was writing in &amp;ldquo;and if we love our souls,&amp;rdquo; when a lady begged at the door for her daughter who suffers from cancer, and said she made little money.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(2.) I said we did not even have it for us, and she unquestioningly left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(3.) Immediately I was troubled in spirit, and called, &amp;ldquo;Lady!&amp;rdquo; and she returned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(4.) I asked her if she believed in God, and she replied that if she was not she would not even be here anymore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(5.) I asked them if they would accept a prayer, and they accepted it well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(6.) I told not to trust in me, but in God, and I began the prayer remembering how I am flawed and that at that moment God used me and put his anointing and words on me,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(7.) How he used that colt to say, indeed, to reproduce his words to that people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(8.) I prayed, and with a little fear, but I overcame the love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(9.) I thanked God for those two souls, and I remembered now that today I was conscious of two women I saw on the street crying and I did not help.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(10.) I had put fear above love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(11.) And everything I write is associated with the things I thought, I said, and I wrote today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(12.) If I had the courage to pray for two strangers (today I spoke about &amp;ldquo;strangers&amp;rdquo;) and disobey my mother and her love, who instructed me not to speak to such people,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(13.) It was not for my merit or courage, but for the mercy and longsuffering of God that I should cast off the diabolical shyness and fear, for the sake of something higher: love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(14.) And in the prayer I spoke about my timidity, and that this comes from the devil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(15.) I hated myself and feared God for not helping two souls, but I loved and thanked God for those souls.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(16.) Therefore, brethren, let not your conscience be troubled by your acts of the past, lest by any means fall from the grace of our Lord Jesus Christ.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(17.) For in grace is love, and in love there is no fear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(18.) If we possess true and complete love, we are a new creature and better things than the past will do, good things standing out against the bad;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(19.) For the person we are today is better and does not compare with that of before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(20.) Therefore, brethren, with love I must repeat:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(21.) If you are no longer that person, but a new one (with that Jesus is happy, for you) feel the freedom and confidence of Jesus Christ, the faith that works by love,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(22.) And do not fear and regret your conscience for that which you have already repented, Jesus has already forgiven you and today you do better things to make up for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(23.) But one thing I say: a lost soul is not made up for, for a single soul is worth more than the whole world, whether it be our soul or that of another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(24.) And I have failed to succor two souls, and to preach the gospel to double souls. Look how serious it is!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(25.) But I did better than before, as a new creature that I am becoming as I wait to be baptized in the waters and to descend into them my old self,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(26.) And for the love of God and my soul I keep my labor for Christ, in a pure conscience and ready to do good things always.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(27.) I have sinned more than all of you, knowing the value of a soul, but this knowledge was not bound to understanding and love, in Spirit and truth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(28.) I feared as I began to write this phrase, but God answered and confirmed that I can not weigh my conscience, for the old creature is an old creature, and the new creature is a new creature;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(29.) So is she is she, and I am I, and the old creature does not disturb the love and faith of the new.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(30.) So what matters today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(31.) Will we sin today hoping to ask for forgiveness tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(32.) Not at all; for the day that Jesus returns is today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(33.) Love yourself and your neighbor as if it were the last day of the world today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(34.) And loving your neighbor, these little ones, you are already loving Jesus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(35.) These things were in my head, but I forgot them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(36.) I began to write this with laziness, weariness, anger, discouragement, doubt, and other similar feelings,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(37.) But now I write all I want (the will comes from the Spirit) and with high speed, like never before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(38.) And today I understand one thing, which was very heavy on my conscience: why we came to Blumenau.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(39.) I stopped at &amp;ldquo;And today I understand&amp;rdquo; and I fed, and the devil began to blow doubts and saying that I was trapped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(40.) But God answered me and said that as he made me write in a letter, I can not trust in the appearance of the world, in the affairs of this earth, nor in the appearance of evil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-5&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 5&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1.) As it is written, love does not suspect evil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(2.) And: the love of Christ constrains us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(3.) Psalm 119: 116 also asks the Lord not to let us be ashamed of our hope.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(4.) Now we shall be ashamed to hope for a higher being among men in an evil world,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(5.) Or will we be ashamed before this higher being for the glory of men who, like us, live for less than 100 years?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(6.) Let us therefore be constrained and humbled with Christ and his cross, and glorified by our faith which brings us certainties and the love that comforts us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(7.) Do you look like a clown who speaks to himself and believes in the invisible?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(8.) Does the world mock you and make you think you are working in vain?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(9.) Has the science of this universe confused you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(10.) There seems to be no one else like you, and you feel like a weirdo?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(11.) Do you seem to diminish while the world seems to grow larger?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(12.) For the appearance of evil and this world persuades us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(13.) The father of lies, who is cunning and possesses the power of death; this is the prince of this world, and he is the god of this century.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(14.) This world is a test, and in it we men (so I also speak of women) choose to bow to the flesh and fear this temporary world, or ascend to the Spirit and love the God of ages and Father of eternity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(15.) Now there is a lie in this world:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(16.) Men laugh and show themselves strong but are afraid of dying;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(17.) Men are honest and pious, but they put money above all else;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(18.) Men drink and show themselves to be happy; but they are there for sorrow;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(19.) Men are wise men and teachers of science; but deny the spirituality and madness of the greatest wisdom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(20.) After writing this, at dinner the devil was angry and wanted to convince me that people thought I did not pray as I should, and I know it,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(21.) But I am not troubled by my faults, nor by what they think of me, but the faith and love of God and his testimonies are my counselors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-6&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 6&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1.) When God touched this in my heart and felt the peace of God, the devil became angry and tempted me by doubts about the existence of God.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(2.) But I thank God for the day when I received a greater science than most men;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(3.) Concerning the existence, the mind of God, her purposes and her love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(4.) And if I do not understand the fullness of God, I am satisfied and satisfied with it;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(5.) For us, mere men in this world, there is a limit to all things, so that our wisdom also has a limit because it is limited while the wisdom of God is infinite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(6.) Can we doubt the existence of God because we can not understand it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(7.) Not at all; for our greatest wisdom is to know that our wisdom is not wisdom, but it is a limited knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(8.) And part of this wisdom is to know that this world will pass away, but we will be resurrected by faith and love;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(9.) In the grace of Jesus Christ, the Son of God, our Lord, and the first fruits of all creatures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(10.) And if I failed to do something good, comfort me in knowing that good intention is greater than failure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(11.) 18/03/2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(12.) Everything that is physical, finite, and flawed comes from him who is spiritual, infinite, and perfect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(13.) She is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(14.) For what is she?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(15.) Whether we call it God, Father, Creator, Lord, Universe, Master; or interpret it as another god, it remains what it is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(16.) She is what she is, she is the &lt;strong&gt;I am&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(17.) If we exist, it is because she is, and we are fruits of her imagination;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(18.) See how great is this power, the fruits of its imagination being so real!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(19.) And we are, but if we are, we are in Her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(20.) Now if you create beings in your imagination, no one believes them, but you are you and only you in your mind and not other person, therefore soon these beings exist!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(21.) And so we are in the mind of God; we are in her womb and beyond exist we are all real.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(22.) God serves us, but not as a servant but as the provider.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(23.) And we serve as servants of the flesh or servants of God.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(24.) And we can only speak as free, overcoming love over all things, with faith as the motor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(25.) The peace, wisdom and love of God be with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(26.) Pray that Jesus will pour out his Spirit with his virtues upon us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(27.) Fight in prayer for me and for your loved ones, and so I will, praying for mine and for receiving this letter (and for yours).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(28.) Do not let the world persuade you by its appearance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(29.) Do not give up on Her who does not give up on you, nor give up on living, because all the time of this test is with God and suicide is a most grievous sin;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(30.) For as you have not decided upon the beginning of this test (your birth) you can not decide to end it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(31.) Do not be distracted by the things of this world, but put spiritual things as a priority.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(32.) Be not negligent in regard to your health, for your body is the temple of the Lord, and he who is negligent toward it also commits a most grievous sin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(33.) Do not doubt God, for I doubted and today she answered us with thunder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(34.) Ask God to reveal your sins that are hidden from you, confess them and try to be a new creature.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(35.) Have your pleasure in praying, seeking knowledge, evangelizing and blessing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(36.) &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:mssdaniellmesquita@gmail.com&#34;&gt;mssdaniellmesquita@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(37.) Blumenau, 03/19/18&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4th Letter to the Matinhos</title>
      <link>/en/2019/06/4th-letter-to-the-matinhos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 14:33:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/2019/06/4th-letter-to-the-matinhos/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-1&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1.) God told me to write a second letter the same day.
(2.) Until I understand this, because on February 21 I began to have existential doubts.
(3.) I would not like to speak in that tone to you, but the present personal need urges me to share with you.
(4.) My weakness makes me understand yours, and makes you identifiable to my feelings.
(5.) I am not in a hurry or lazy to write this letter, for the world is bad, apparent, disappointing, hopeless, full of hatred, greed and confusion.
(6.) Not everyone had the opportunity to realize what I noticed about the world.
(7.) For me, living is bordering on impossibility, and the world is rejecting me from even when I was of the world.
(8.) The world does not know that a group of men controls it with three influences, and this group (confraternity, order, sect, organization, brotherhood) does not know who rules them.
(9.) &amp;ldquo;Deliver much, get the rest, smile&amp;rdquo; (in the world).
(10.) And: &amp;ldquo;Bite, chew, swallow, repeat.&amp;rdquo;
(11.) And: &amp;ldquo;get used to joking, cheating, disappointments, study, grow, work, envy, eat and drink, age, die&amp;rdquo;.
(12.) The first and second are rules of the subconsciousness of the world and transcribed them to the conscience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-2&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 2&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1.) The world is attractive, exciting, promising, thought-provoking, possessive.
(2.) We want to be happy; money gives power of movements;
(3.) We feel productive when awake; we feel unproductive when we look at the time but trust the other day;
(4.) We see the capacity for growth of others and we may feel inferior; dreams bring motivation and pleasure;
(5.) Excessive appearance or desire brings confidence;
(6.) The struggle carries hope and love for a cause;
(7.) Love makes us coexist, converge, and feel pleasure in each other and in each other;
(8.) The streets are full of men and women of great attractiveness;
(9.) Beautiful women impress men, and the friction and tightness in the volume of their body is very pleasing;
(10.) A new time is a hope deposited and things attributed;
(11.) Hope shows meaning and holds us steady;
(12.) Pride makes us feel normal;
(13.) Ego and fury are primal feelings but are attractive to many and make them feel secure;
(14.) Using the new version of a product excites us and keeps us engaged;
(15.) High palatability foods and beverages are at our disposal to delight in every piece, filling, layer, coating, sugar conglomerate, salt grain, fat gel, and drop, and aromas, and textures, and flavors;
(16.) Superstitions reassure us and make us feel power and power;
(17.) Shame and passions keep us connected to our appearance and this, makes us feel good.
(18.) I could talk about more delicious things, but I would get excited and throw up rainbows; but I&amp;rsquo;m not here to have love for the world, and even less to draw you into the world.
(19.) Nevertheless, when it comes to appearance, all this I mentioned is appearance and illusions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[From here, Daniell began to write in smaller and smaller letters.]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(20.) Are you blind not to see this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Then the letters got even smaller, requiring a good magnifier to be able to read.]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(21.) Without contradictions, I tell you, even though I have no academic background in letters: it is with great letters that I write to you.
(22.) Jesus Christ is the zoom of existence and of things to come.
(23.) Appearances disappoint, fevers lower, animals go extinct, humans die and celestial bodies threaten us.
(24.) But all this limitation is a sample: they are shadows of things to come.
(25.) But we must reject these samples, to have the reals.
(26.) For Christ was rejected for the sake of it.
(27.) But other people only want to spend, without giving thanks to the God who created them with love.
(28.) And she also wants the love of our part, for ourselves, for she has given us the fuel of love so that we can do it for ourselves.
(29.) Like atoms, all creation has the same origin and dependence, so they should drop blindness and embrace in this pain of non-obvious but common birth and wait for the birth of the new body.
(30.) But he who is blind can not see in his neighbor, that like you, he is a member of the same body dependent on these members.
(31.) And we are the body of Christ in the flesh, the flesh that was crucified (and that flesh is crucified when we forsake our sins).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-3&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 3&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1.) I do not care to be blind in the flesh for writing thus, for if it is to bring spiritual sight to you, it is just.
(2.) Perhaps you are getting in the way of the lines of this letter, but you are also getting in the way, and the lines are:
(3.) Illusions, cares, doubts, anger, desires, fears, fatigue, sadness, laziness, and others similar to these.
(4.) I ask you to discover some mysteries of truth, without laziness and without discouragement, but with love and dedication.
(5.) What is easier to believe: that I am Chapolin Colorado writing after ingesting one of my famous cold-paced thumbscrews, or that I am the inspired scribble of God?
(6.) What is easier to believe: that God is an atom that has come together and made existence and the universe win in the lottery with the coincidence of being us and the only rational in the universe (according to the Bible) or that God Who created it?
(7.) It is easier to believe in the revolution of atoms than to believe in the revolution of the Left, because man is the most flawed but God is perfect.
(8.) As for political, religious, sporting, moral, philosophical, scientific, ideological differences among men: they are vain disputes of men lacking in understanding.
(9.) Revolution? It will be the coming of Christ to seek His people.
(10.) I understand why my father wanted me, even my mother was 39 years old.
(11.) I am of a generation that is informed, that likes philosophy, that seeks knowledge, that it feels revulsion against the folly and ignorance.
(12.) Perhaps I am one of the most avid of my generation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-4&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 4&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1.) If you laughed when I said to be the Chapolin Colorado to write, and thought &amp;ldquo;will?&amp;quot;: This is a playful belief.
(2.) Like scholars who like the Greek gods even though they do not believe in godliness.
(3.) But if something presents itself as real (like the God of the Bible), it is hated; and what is presented as playful is loved.
(4.) And, unfortunately: many are evangelicals, Catholics and others who &amp;ldquo;believe&amp;rdquo; in a playful and symbolic way.
(5.) I wake up with sleep, and sleep all day, and when night approaches I begin to shake.
(6.) So is the drunkard, who drinks all night, in the undertow repents, and then drinks again.
(7.) So do not be you: sinning, suffering and repenting, and after the trauma, sin again;
(8.) But have the same spirit, personal and common, in itself and with each other.
(9.) And when you are fallen, know that it is to rise, and look, do not stumble.
(10.) For Christ had to be lifted up, and to be lifted he had to go down.
(11.) Did the Pokémon show the Charizard ready, or to be amused has it been shown since it was a long-suffering Charmander abandoned?
(12.) Charizard did not have to almost die to tie the tie with Ash Ketchum?
(13.) The Butterfree who wins the Pewter gym, not of grace when we remember that before it was only a Caterpie that suffered?
(14.) So it is in our grace with Christ toward God.
(15.) A weak object, thrown into the water, buoy;
(16.) The heavy sinks;
(17.) But the moderate sinks and then rises.
(18.) So let&amp;rsquo;s be moderate.
(19.) Who is Christ? God needed a form for himself,
(20.) &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:mssdaniellmesquita@gmail.com&#34;&gt;mssdaniellmesquita@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;
(21.) Matinhos, 04/21/18&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4th song by Daniell Mesquita</title>
      <link>/en/2019/06/4th-song-by-daniell-mesquita/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 14:33:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/2019/06/4th-song-by-daniell-mesquita/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;stronger-than-wine&#34;&gt;Stronger than wine&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1.) How could God be, if he did not love exist?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(2.) Without love, nothing would exist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(3.) And before God created us, God loves to exist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(4.) Love is the reason for existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(5.) God is in us, feeling everything we feel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(6.) And before we love him, he loved us, and still loves, and will always love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(7.) And how does God feel, when we do not forgive who he loves?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(8.) We are all bodies of God, we embrace in this pain, until the new body of our Lord comes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(9.) Ah, the love is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(10.) Drink stronger than wine; a song more beautiful than that of a bird;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(11.) One does not learn by reading a parchment; from the cradle you have the affection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(12.) Love you eat, eat, eat and do not vomit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(13.) Love you eat, eat, eat and grows lighter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(14.) Love you drink, drink, drink and do not get dizzy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(15.) Love you drink, drink, drink and become more and more lucid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(16.) Jesus is the bread of life, and love is the bread of the soul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(17.) Wine is the liquid of the body, and love is the liquid of the soul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(18.) Love is not in physical attraction, love sees the inner; it is soul love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(19.) God does not care about our differences, but with our soul; and let our love be in the soul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(20.) In love there is no debauchery; in love there is sincere, joyful and innocent laughter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(21.) Love celebrates and admires good things, and does not become blind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(22.) Love is living feeling, and quickens everything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(23.) Love is the meaning of life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(24.) Oh, the love is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(25.) Drink stronger than wine; song more beautiful than a bird.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(26.) You can not learn by reading a parchment; from the cradle you have the affection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(27.) Love you eat, eat, eat and do not vomit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(28.) Love you eat, eat, eat and grows lighter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(29.) Love you drink, drink, drink and do not get dizzy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(30.) Love you drink, drink, drink and become more and more lucid.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adults - 1st letter to the Blumenauans</title>
      <link>/en/2019/06/adults-1st-letter-to-the-blumenauans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 14:33:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/2019/06/adults-1st-letter-to-the-blumenauans/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../../img/letters/blumenauans/1.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-1&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1.) Hi! I understand that it is impolite to read the letter which is for others, but this letter is for you, who found it out there after I threw it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(2.) I hope these words are very useful to you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(3.) Sorry if I disturbed your rush, but my intention is to build you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(4.) In ancient times, people had more time and did more things, and lived for more years, but in modern times people run a lot, feel that they have not produced enough and that time is lacking in every day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(5.) Nowadays people have great infrastructure and medical care, but in contrast the lifestyle and industrialized foods (snacks, fast food, etc.) have reduced people&amp;rsquo;s life expectancy, while &amp;ldquo;fit&amp;rdquo; foods are more expensive and considered, perhaps, by the majority as having a lower flavor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(6.) But speaking in ancient times: people were more dedicated to reading a letter they found.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(7.) They read with humility, attention, interest, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(8.) I ask that you be like this when reading this letter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(9.) When reading, you may think, &amp;ldquo;crazy!&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Another one of those&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;tongue&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;liar&amp;rdquo;, but read it with much love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-2&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 2&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1.) Love and faith are gratuitous, and are the greatest things that exist in the Universe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(2.) Love is the greatest gift of beings, and faith is the greatest mover on earth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(3.) What about wisdom? Proverbs 4: 7: &amp;ldquo;Wisdom is the chief thing: get wisdom, use all that you possess in gaining understanding.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(4.) And if all you have is faith?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(5.) It is in faith that you can acquire wisdom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(6.) James 1: 5: &amp;ldquo;And if any of you lacks wisdom, let him ask of God, who giveth to all men liberally, and casteth him not, and it shall be given him.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(7.) If wisdom is the main thing, do I mistake in saying that faith is the greatest mover?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(8.) No, for with faith one acquires the chief thing called Wisdom, so faith is also chief, all of these being important in their functions, as members of a body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(9.) 1 Corinthians 11:11: &amp;ldquo;Neither is a man without the woman, nor the woman without the man, in the Lord.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(10.) 1 Corinthians 11:12: &amp;ldquo;For as the woman is of the man, so also the man is of the woman: but all things are of God.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(11.) 1 Corinthians 12: 20-21: &amp;ldquo;Therefore there are many members, but one body: and the eye can not say by the hand, I have no need of thee, neither yet head to my feet: I have no need of you &amp;ldquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(12.) Thinking of a weaker member, and if that is your faith?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(13.) If your faith is small? Matthew 17:20: &amp;ldquo;And Jesus saith unto them, Because of your low faith: for verily I say unto you, If ye have faith as a grain of mustard seed, ye shall say unto this mountain: pass over thither, and pass over; nothing will be impossible for you. &amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(14.) Do not read this with debauchery, for obviously even though your faith is a giant, you can not move a hill, for it is not God&amp;rsquo;s will.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(15.) 1 John 5:14, &amp;ldquo;And this is the confidence which we have in him, that if we ask anything according to his will, he heareth us.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(16.) What if you ask for something that is not God&amp;rsquo;s will? James 4: 3: &amp;ldquo;Ye ask, and receive not, because ye ask evilly, that ye may spend it in your pleasures.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(17.) Did you ask for a good thing and not receive it? Do not think that you asked badly, nor give up; insist, for in the time of God he does for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(18.) Jesus said in Luke 18: 7, &amp;ldquo;Shall not God execute judgment upon his elect, who cry unto him day and night, though he tarry with them?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(19.) Read Matthew 17:20 again in this same letter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(20.) Is your faith small, the size of a mustard seed? Matthew 13: 31-32: &amp;ldquo;And he spake another parable unto them, saying, The kingdom of heaven is like unto the grain of mustard seed, which a man hath taken in him, sowing in his field: which is the least of all the seeds; but it is the greatest of plants, and a tree is made, so that the birds of the air come and nest in their branches. &amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(21.) For if your faith is small, but you have faith!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(22.) And your faith can be exercised to grow much more, even in faith you may ask for more faith.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(23.) &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:mssdaniellmesquita@gmail.com&#34;&gt;mssdaniellmesquita@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Children - 5th song by Daniell Mesquita</title>
      <link>/en/2019/06/children-5th-song-by-daniell-mesquita/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 14:33:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/2019/06/children-5th-song-by-daniell-mesquita/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-little-ones-of-jesus&#34;&gt;My little ones of Jesus&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1.) My little ones of Jesus:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(2.) Hearken unto this little brother, and follow the way of God your Father.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(3.) God of David, is also the God of You.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(4.) Jesus of Nazareth is also the Jesus of Heaven.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(5.) God of Israel, also God of Brazil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(6.) Jehovah is also called Existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(7.) The Spirit of Jesus rounds the earth, and is welcoming all the little ones on the hem of their garments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(8.) With much love he caresses his little children, and comforts and comforts hearts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(9.) Jesus is more beautiful than all flowers;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(10.) Jesus is sweeter than all honey;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(11.) Jesus is kinder than a lamb;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(12.) Jesus is more loving than your kitten.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(13.) My little ones of Jesus:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(14.) Hearken unto this little brother, and follow the way of God your Father.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(15.) God of David, is also the God of You.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(16.) Jesus of Nazareth is also the Jesus of Heaven.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(17.) God of Israel, is also the God of Brazil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(18.) Jehovah is also called Existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(19.) There is a crystal clear river, and the sound of the waters calms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(20.) There is a garden, the most beautiful, God guards as a treasure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(21.) There is a heaven full of angels, and Jesus Christ reigns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(22.) There is a people here who adore you, Lord, and expect to be adopted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(23.) His children are his angels on earth;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(24.) Your song, we love it very much;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(25.) Your smiles, comfort and renew your whole soul;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(26.) And in the brightness of their eyes the adults can see many things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(27.) My little ones of Jesus:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(28.) Hearken unto this little brother, and follow the way of God your Father.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(29.) God of David, is also the God of You.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(30.) Jesus of Nazareth is also the Jesus of Heaven.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(31.) God of Israel, also God of Brazil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(32.) Jehovah is also called Existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(33.) God knows everything about everything and everyone;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(34.) Before you were you, God knew you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(35.) God knows what you feel and need;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(36.) But we still pray, for this is a pleasant sacrifice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(37.) Jesus is kinder than your grandmother;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(38.) Jesus is more loving than your puppy;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(39.) Jesus is more beautiful than anything and everyone;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(40.) Jesus is sweeter than all chocolate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(41.) My little ones of Jesus:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(42.) Hearken unto this little brother, and follow the way of God your Father.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(43.) God of David is also the God of You.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(44.) Jesus of Nazareth is also the Jesus of Heaven.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(45.) God of Israel, also God of Brazil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(46.) ​​​​Jehovah is also called Existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(47.) God chose dumb things to confound the wise;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(48.) God chose the weak things to confound the strong;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(49.) God made the poor richer than the millionaires;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(50.) God knows your little ones are big.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(51.) There is the Earth, where humans are small;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(52.) There is the Universe, where the Earth is so small;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(53.) There is Heaven, where the Universe is microscopic;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(54.) There is God, where Heaven has no size.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(55.) My little ones of Jesus: pay attention to this little brother and follow the way of God your Father.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(56.) God of David, is also the God of You.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(57.) Jesus of Nazareth is also the Jesus of Heaven.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(58.) God of Israel, he is also the God of Brazil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(59.) Jehovah is also called Existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(60.) My little ones of God: pay attention to this little brother and follow the way of Jesus.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversations - Chat 1</title>
      <link>/en/2019/06/conversations-chat-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 14:33:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/2019/06/conversations-chat-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;chat-with-misc-in-pokémon-online&#34;&gt;Chat with Misc in &lt;strong&gt;Pokémon Online&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;note-if-you-dont-understand-english--spanish-you-can-read-the-next-dialogues-chat-2-etc-or-if-you-dont-like-dialogues-you-can-read-letters-or-songs&#34;&gt;description: &amp;gt;-
&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;: if you don&amp;rsquo;t understand English / Spanish, you can read the next dialogues (chat 2, etc.), or if you don&amp;rsquo;t like dialogues, you can read letters or songs.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;03/29/18&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:42) Daniell: Hey&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:42) Miss Lucy Love x: hi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:43) Daniell: Do you usually plays Pokémon here?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:46) Miss Lucy Love x: yea&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:54) Daniell: Whats your religion?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:54) Daniell: I&amp;rsquo;m sorry for this question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:05) Miss Lucy Love x: don&amp;rsquo;t have religion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:07) Daniell: Some months ago I also has no religion. Do you want to know what was my position against religion?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:08) Miss Lucy Love x: I&amp;rsquo;m sorry but I hate religion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:09) Miss Lucy Love x: stupid pointless rules made up by a fake creature&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:10) Daniell: You is in atheism or just no religion?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:12) Miss Lucy Love x: no religion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:14) Daniell: But do you believe that all of this are from a creator?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:14) Daniell: For sample, that we are in a supercomputer right now or something like?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:21) Miss Lucy Love x: fuck no&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:21) Miss Lucy Love x: I belive in science&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:21) Miss Lucy Love x: the big bang&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:22) Daniell: Do you want to know my position against religion?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:24) Miss Lucy Love x: what&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:43) Miss Lucy Love x: yed&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:43) Miss Lucy Love x: yes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:49) Daniell: Sorry, I was talking with a latin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:49) Daniell: I will say to you&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:50) Daniell: I was a religious, in the christianism. But I saw the fathers doing very bad things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:50) Daniell: Fathers, no. What are the name of these that are of the evangelicism?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:43) Daniell: Hi?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:48) Miss Lucy Love x: hey&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:48) Miss Lucy Love x: I call em idiotic sheeple&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:49) Daniell: No so idiotic, because they have so much &amp;ldquo;smartness&amp;rdquo; to manipulate people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:50) Daniell: One of these, talked to the people, when I was in the church: &amp;ldquo;you all will be rich in the next week&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:51) Daniell: And we don&amp;rsquo;t has more money, so I started to doubt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:51) Daniell: I saw other negative things, then I abandonned the religion and I began to atheism/agnosticism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:43) Daniell: Hey&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:46) Miss Farrelly: hi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:46) Daniell: Do you usually plays Pokémon here?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:49) Miss Farrelly: yes i do hun&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:54) Daniell: Whats your religion?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:57) Miss Farrelly: wiccan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:04) Daniell: What is this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:04) Miss Farrelly: its a pagan religion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:05) Daniell: Wich things you learned in this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:05) Daniell: Which*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:28) The other party left the server, so the window was disabled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:42) Daniell: Hey&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:00) [GTX] Legendary Ký: heyy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:04) Daniell: Do you have faith in something supernatural?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:05) [GTX] Legendary Ký: you mean like a god yeah i would believe so&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:11) Daniell: Just in a God that created all, or you believe in your Son?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:11) Daniell: your&amp;gt;his*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:12) [GTX] Legendary Ký: yes i believe im his son&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:13) Daniell: Yes, you is son of the Creator. But do you believe in his Son? I mean, the Christ.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:14) [GTX] Legendary Ký: yeah i believe in Jesus&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:15) Daniell: In which things the christian churchs make you scared? Can you list?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:17) [GTX] Legendary Ký: mostly going to hell and such things as that im not a overaly religious guy but i do have a belief there is such a being a jesus Christ&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:17) Daniell: What makes me scared about this are: the love in the money, the voice scadals to attract people and the manipulations in Bible reading. But the worst in this list is: love in the money. We need to love people above all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:18) Daniell: And the list is greater, and like you said: mostly are being missed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:18) Daniell: The churchs aren&amp;rsquo;t anymore the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:19) Daniell: I believe its a signal of the return of Christ.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:19) Daniell: Earthquakes, wars and war rumors, signals from sky (here in Brazil we saw a lot this year), the churchs with corruption, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:21) [GTX] Legendary Ký: i see do you ever think things will change&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:25) Daniell: What do you think about this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:31) [GTX] Legendary Ký: well here in American its been less than the same depending where you go from my experiences its been really hard snd and as you said the church hadn&amp;rsquo;t been the same i do think better is coming it&amp;rsquo;s just a matter of when&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:36) Daniell: It can be funny to hear, but most of churchs today are creating atheists instead of putting faith and truth in the hearts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:36) Daniell: And teaching the hate instead of the most perfect feeling: the love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:36) Daniell: The love is being each time more rare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:37) Daniell: And what is rare, have a great value. And the love is the most rare, so is the most valuable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:37) Daniell: Like said in Bible: the love is the link to perfection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:38) Daniell: The love is more rare than the faith. And the faith is more rare than smartness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:42) Daniell: Hey&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:42) [RMX-L] El Bravo: que onda&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:43) Daniell: ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:43) [RMX-L] El Bravo: ¿te conozco?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:44) Daniell: No, pero conoces a Jesus?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:44) [RMX-L] El Bravo: ¿cual jesus?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:44) Daniell: El Nazareno.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:44) Daniell: Son muchos Jesus hoy, no?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:44) [RMX-L] El Bravo: ¿vienes a predicar al po?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:44) [RMX-L] El Bravo: jajajaa&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:46) Daniell: ¿Que te pasas a respecho de el cristianismo?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:46) [RMX-L] El Bravo: pues yo soy neutral&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:46) [RMX-L] El Bravo: cada quien es libre de profesar la fe que le convenga&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:46) Daniell: Bueno.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:47) [RMX-L] El Bravo: pero yo siento que po no es un lugar idoneo para predicar y menos a un tipo que no conoces jaja&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:48) Daniell: Yo no conosco ustedes, pero mi Jesus conoces sus pensamientos del corazon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:49) Daniell: Soy brazileno y mi espanol no es bueno, pero de Dios venga la inspiracion de su Espirito.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:52) [RMX-L] El Bravo: pues si mi amigo espero estes bien&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:53) Daniell: ¿Que cosas te hacieran neutral?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:54) [RMX-L] El Bravo: pues simplemente he aprendido&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:54) [RMX-L] El Bravo: que debemos respetarnos los unos a los otros&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:54) [RMX-L] El Bravo: y sin importar que fe porfese el otro mientras el sea feliz y no perjudique a nadie haya el&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:55) Daniell: En verdade te hablo, haces mejor que muchos predicadores de Cristo!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:56) [RMX-L] El Bravo: pues esa es la verdad&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:56) [RMX-L] El Bravo: hasta en la biblia viene en mateo 6&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:57) [RMX-L] El Bravo: las iglesias evangelicas solo manipulan a las masas solo usando las partes de la biblia segun les conviene&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:57) [RMX-L] El Bravo: y ellos hacen un escandalo con sus &amp;ldquo;oraciones&amp;rdquo; y en mateo viene como es la oracion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:00) Daniell: Muchos intentan ganar personas con escandalos, pero no hacen como conviene a Dios: ganar almas en amor. Pero, lo dinhero es la cosa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:01) Daniell: Las iglesias no son mas como antes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:03) Daniell: Yo fue AntiCristo, pero Dios creou cosas en mi vision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:04) [RMX-L] El Bravo: oh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:04) [RMX-L] El Bravo: ¿eres vidente acaso?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:07) Daniell: No se. Mi padre fue vidente.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:08) Daniell: No cosas de vidente, pero yo conoci a el Satanas en mi visions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:09) Daniell: Yo puedo te hablar: el Diabo es un dios, tamano su poder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:23) [RMX-L] El Bravo: por mi neutralidad&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:23) [RMX-L] El Bravo: se de cosas esotericas un poco&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:24) [RMX-L] El Bravo: y creo que si las cosas son como dices&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:24) [RMX-L] El Bravo: es que mucha gente duda de su fe&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:24) [RMX-L] El Bravo: probablemente sea por eso&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:29) Daniell: Yo dudo las veces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:29) [RMX-L] El Bravo: segun lo que he estudiado&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:29) Daniell: Pero no es por las dudas de la gente; pero yo conoci Satanas por mi dudas en el supernatural.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:30) [RMX-L] El Bravo: pues eso es lo que busca el enemigo&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:30) [RMX-L] El Bravo: que dudes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:30) [RMX-L] El Bravo: para meterse por ahi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:30) [RMX-L] El Bravo: entonces intuyo que tus visiones te hicieron buscarme&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:33) Daniell: Si, dices la verdad como quien reciebe el Espirito para reproducir las sabias palavras; el enemigo pos dudas y yo pense en intentar contra mi vida ha uns meses. Pero las visiones no fue actuales.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:34) [RMX-L] El Bravo: ¿y que viste referente a mi persona?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:34) [RMX-L] El Bravo: ¿porque estas aqui ahora?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:34) Daniell: Hablo contigo en amor de Cristo para tu conocer la verdad, pero vejo que tienes un muy bueno conocimento.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:35) [RMX-L] El Bravo: pues muchos leen&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:35) [RMX-L] El Bravo: pocos analizan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:39) Daniell: Lo que no entienden, dizen que es de manos de lo hombre.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:39) Daniell: Y lo que conviene, aceptan y predican a los otros a oprimir o ganar dinero.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:40) Daniell: O exibir que son de Cristo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:41) Daniell: Hoy e muy belo exibir que es de una iglesia, que tienes una bela familia, que tienes sucesso en todas las cosas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:41) [RMX-L] El Bravo: yo un dia estaba viendo versiculos de la biblia pues quiero estaratento para responderle a los dichosos &amp;ldquo;predicadores&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:41) [RMX-L] El Bravo: y de hecho cristo vino para abolir los templos&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:41) [RMX-L] El Bravo: porque si te fijas en el nuevo testamento&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:41) [RMX-L] El Bravo: la situacion en la que jesus llego al mundo&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:41) [RMX-L] El Bravo: no se dista mucho de la actualidad&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:42) Daniell: Pero los tienpos dificultam&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:43) Daniell: Las iglesis hoy eston con mas cosas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:43) Daniell: Y hoy predican lo sucesso&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:43) Daniell: Pero las pisadas de Cristo no son somiente eso&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:43) [RMX-L] El Bravo: los sumos sacerdotes judios cobraban y lucraban con las leyes de moises&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:44) [RMX-L] El Bravo: ¿y que hacen los sacerdotes y pastores hoy?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:44) Daniell: Lo mismo, pero con las leyes de Dios, y, del amor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:44) Daniell: Ha muchos hablando en amor, pero no amando las personas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:45) [RMX-L] El Bravo: distorcionadas a su convenencias&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:45) [RMX-L] El Bravo: porque jesus vino a abolir todo eso&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:45) [RMX-L] El Bravo: pero como ellos no prestan atencion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:45) [RMX-L] El Bravo: o se hacen tontos (lo que yo creo)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:45) Daniell: Y los pastores de hoy no quieren que las personas saian a otras iglesias, como numa competicion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:46) Daniell: Hoy predican lo que las personas quieren ouvir: liberdad y sucesso.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:46) Daniell: Y se no tienen sucesso, dudan de dios.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:47) [RMX-L] El Bravo: imponen reglas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:47) [RMX-L] El Bravo: igual que los sacerdotes judios&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:47) Daniell: pero no las sieguen&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:48) Daniell: quieren ver las personas circuncidadas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:48) Daniell: y obedeciendo a los hombres&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:48) Daniell: y olvidando a Dios&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:48) Daniell: la Biblia predictou a eso&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:48) Daniell: como a muchas cosas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:51) [RMX-L] El Bravo: en hechos de los apostoles viene eso&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:53) Daniell: Tu familia, tambien son neutrales?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:53) Daniell: Mi familia es dividida in todos los sentidos.]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:53) [RMX-L] El Bravo: como hubo en el pueblo profetas falsos asi habra falsos doctores que intrduciran sectas perniciosas que llegaran hasta a negar al señor&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:54) [RMX-L] El Bravo: mi abuela era catolica&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:54) [RMX-L] El Bravo: mis padres no pertenecian a ninguna religion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:54) [RMX-L] El Bravo: podria decirse que son neutrales pero creen en dios&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:54) Daniell: y si amontoarian falsos doctores confuerme los desejos de las personas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:54) [RMX-L] El Bravo: claro&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:55) Daniell: Yo no tengo religion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:55) Daniell: Fue evangelico, enton ateista/agnostico.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:55) [RMX-L] El Bravo: pues me considero agnostico&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:55) [RMX-L] El Bravo: pues no creo en religiones&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:55) Daniell: Entonces yo tive las visiones y cri en el supernatural.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:56) [RMX-L] El Bravo: pero creo que hay un poder mayor&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:56) Daniell: Yo no cri en lo mismo Dios de la Biblia en el agnosticismo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:56) [RMX-L] El Bravo: poder mayor= dios&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:56) Daniell: y creador de todo&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:57) Daniell: Dios es la existencia, la eternidad, la razon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:57) Daniell: Para mi fue muy dificil entender eso&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:57) [RMX-L] El Bravo: claro&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:57) Daniell: Yo vire ateu muchas veces&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:57) Daniell: Pero el Espirito pos me palavras&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:58) Daniell: Y yo pude entendier&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:59) [RMX-L] El Bravo: es mas checa este video&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:59) [RMX-L] El Bravo: ahi viene lo que te acabo de decir&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:59) [RMX-L] El Bravo: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=csoJCR47ueU&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=csoJCR47ueU&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:00) Daniell: Cres en demonios?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:01) Daniell: Ahora es 3 de la noche, y dizen que los espiritos malos rodean.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:02) [RMX-L] El Bravo: si crees en dios no puedes creer en otra cosa&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:02) Daniell: Yo nunca vi espiritos, pero yo vejo su poder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:02) [RMX-L] El Bravo: si les haces caso&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:02) [RMX-L] El Bravo: los haras mas fuertes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:03) Daniell: Pero se las personas crecen en el poder de lo Diabo, no crerian en el mundo material y buscarian a el Espirito para sobrepor contra los demonios.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:04) [RMX-L] El Bravo: tu mismo lo has dicho&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:04) [RMX-L] El Bravo: pero creer en eso es darle poder&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:05) Daniell: La Biblia habla del poder de lo enemigo. Pero no es para crer como cre en Dios.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:06) [RMX-L] El Bravo: y el objetivo del enemigo&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:06) [RMX-L] El Bravo: es hacer dudar a las personas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:06) [RMX-L] El Bravo: para este incomodar a jehova&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:07) Daniell: este es un de sus objectivos&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:07) Daniell: su major objectivo es cargar almas con el&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:08) Daniell: el enemigo odea a todo que es creacion de dios&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:08) Daniell: Dios*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:08) [RMX-L] El Bravo: las almas que obtiene es porque son ingenuas y se dejan engañar al dudar les falta conviccion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:09) Daniell: o creen en dios, pero otras cosas eston acima, como la gloria de los hombres.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:10) Daniell: la ingenuidad es buena, pero misturada a la sabedoria.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:11) Daniell: Por la ingenuidad alcanza la fe en cosas que no se veen pero se sienten.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:12) Daniell: E en la ingenuidad tienes el puro amor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:13) [RMX-L] El Bravo: de cierta manera si&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:13) Daniell: Paulo hablou sobre eso: meninos en la malicia, y adultos en la sabedoria.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:13) [RMX-L] El Bravo: pero muchos viven ingenuos siempre&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:13) [RMX-L] El Bravo: y engañados&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:13) Daniell: Si, y destes los malos doctores de la fe usan para obtener cosas de la Tierra.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:14) Daniell: Y daron conta de esas almas en lo regresso de Jesus&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:20) [RMX-L] El Bravo: claro&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:21) [RMX-L] El Bravo: porque jesus esta viendo&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:21) [RMX-L] El Bravo: que la humanidad no va como el queria que fuera&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:21) [RMX-L] El Bravo: ni tampoco con lo que el predico original mente&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:25) Daniell: No toda la humanidad. Y Jesus sabia que esas cosas virian a el mundo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:26) [RMX-L] El Bravo: claro&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:26) [RMX-L] El Bravo: no toda&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:26) [RMX-L] El Bravo: pero hablaba en metafora&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:27) Daniell: Crees in Dios sin crer a ninguna religion, pero Jesus es de una religion: el cristianismo. Como crees en Jesus?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:28) [RMX-L] El Bravo: en realidad&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:28) [RMX-L] El Bravo: jesus era judio&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:28) [RMX-L] El Bravo: el cristianimo se fundo por el pero perdio el camino&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:28) [RMX-L] El Bravo: porque por eso se le llama cristianismo&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:31) Daniell: Pero, como crees en Jesus, siendo tu de el agnosticismo?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:32) [RMX-L] El Bravo: pues lo hablo basandome en argumentos de un &amp;ldquo;predicador&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:32) [RMX-L] El Bravo: te aseguro que si a uno de esos le digo lo mismo sale huyendo&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:35) Daniell: Lo entiendo, hablas en el contexto. Pero pense que crias en Jesus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:35) [RMX-L] El Bravo: quizas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:36) [RMX-L] El Bravo: los agnosticon creen en un poder mayor&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:36) [RMX-L] El Bravo: ¿recuerdas?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:36) Daniell: Si.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:36) Daniell: Crer en Dios es mejor que no crer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:37) Daniell: Y mejor no crer, haciendo el bien; que crendo hacer el malo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:37) Daniell: o que, profesando, no seguir y intentar que somiente los otros sigan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:38) [RMX-L] El Bravo: pues si&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:39) [RMX-L] El Bravo: es mejor&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:39) [RMX-L] El Bravo: respetar&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:40) Daniell: Tiengo mas cosas a hablar, pero no tengo como ahora. Esas palavras no son limitadas asi, perdoname.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:46) [RMX-L] El Bravo: si tranquilo suele pasar&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(01:42) The other party left the server, so the window was disabled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:05) The player has logged on again&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:11) Daniell: Hey&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:11) Typhon: hi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:11) The other party left the server, so the window was disabled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:20) The player has logged on again&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:24) Daniell: Do you have a religion?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:25) Typhon: humanity&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:27) Daniell: Sorry for my missknowledge. I had hear about this (my ex friend is of this religion) but I don&amp;rsquo;t know its principles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:27) Daniell: What and how they are? This is like believing in open mind?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:28) Daniell: Something like libertarianism and LGBT/interacial rights?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:41) Typhon: 1 min&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:41) Typhon: i wipp tell u later&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:41) Typhon: i m busy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(02:51) Daniell: Ok, np.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:00) The other party left the server, so the window was disabled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:13) The player has logged on again&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:16) Daniell: Hi, again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:16) Daniell: When available, please say me more about the religion of humanity? I know we have Google, but I want to hear this from a member.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:28) The other party left the server, so the window was disabled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:31) The other party left the server, so the window was disabled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:40) The player has logged on again&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:44) Daniell: ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:44) Typhon: humanity is the greatest religion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:45) Typhon: it is above all religion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:45) Typhon: the first religion of a person is to become a true human&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:46) Typhon: if u r not a true human u r not worth of following any religion&amp;hellip; it will be use less&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:48) Daniell: &amp;ldquo;is to become a true human&amp;rdquo;, it is true. Because who not knows itself, can&amp;rsquo;t believe in so much things. And who don&amp;rsquo;t have a self love, can&amp;rsquo;t love anything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:48) Daniell: Because to be human, the love is needed.]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:29) Daniell: Hi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:29) LIFO: hi?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:29) Daniell: Yes, I don&amp;rsquo;t know you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:30) Daniell: Its strange?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:30) LIFO: kind of?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:30) Daniell: Please don&amp;rsquo;t be shammed about this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:30) Daniell: Do you have a religion?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:30) LIFO: no&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:31) Daniell: Atheism?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:32) LIFO: yeah&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:33) Daniell: I have no strenghts to dispute about this, I&amp;rsquo;m sorry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:33) LIFO: eh&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(03:34) LIFO: all right&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:00) moe: hi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:00) Daniell: Do you believe in a Creator?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:04) moe: wdym?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:05) Daniell: I mean who created the whole universe or, to call, multiverse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:06) moe: oh yeah,i believe&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:06) Daniell: How do you think he is?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:07) moe: im a moslem,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:08) moe: he is beyond everything&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:09) Daniell: Whats your religion?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:11) moe: islam&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:12) Daniell: Do you believe in the love?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:14) moe: mhm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:14) Daniell: ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:14) Daniell: I don&amp;rsquo;t understood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:15) moe: yes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:01) Daniell: Hi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:04) 遇到鬼蝉我要死啦: hi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:04) Daniell: Do you have a religion?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:05) 遇到鬼蝉我要死啦: no&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:06) 遇到鬼蝉我要死啦: why you ask this&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:06) The other party left the server, so the window was disabled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:07) The player has logged on again&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:11) Daniell: Sorry me for this question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:11) Daniell: I&amp;rsquo;m just asking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Daniell tried to evangelize the Chinese, but these usernames with Chinese characteres are fake accounts probably made by Americans; but he wasn&amp;rsquo;t ready and this wasn&amp;rsquo;t the time to evangelize them.]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:11) Daniell: Hi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:11) Corsola: hi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:12) Daniell: Do you have a religion?]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:14) Corsola: yrs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:14) Corsola: yes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:14) Daniell: What?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:15) Corsola: Private&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:16) Daniell: I was atheist/agnostic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:16) Corsola: o&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:16) Corsola: may I know who are you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:18) Daniell: Any person&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:18) Corsola: Then why did you just appear out of nowhere&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:18) Corsola: and ask me that question +&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(04:19) Daniell: Because the souls needs appearin of [to] somewhere.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
