<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>logs on Do you still need a Third Testament?</title>
    <link>/en/categories/logs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in logs on Do you still need a Third Testament?</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>pt-br</language>
    <copyright>Written in 2018 by Daniell Mesquita (https://daniellmesquita.eth.link)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 14:33:54 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/en/categories/logs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2nd letter to the Blumenauans</title>
      <link>/en/2019/06/2nd-letter-to-the-blumenauans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 14:33:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/2019/06/2nd-letter-to-the-blumenauans/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;img/letters/blumenauans/2.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-1&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You do not know when this was written, nor who writes, but know who wants to talk to you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I do not know if you are a man or a woman.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But what does it matter? You are reading, and you can build with it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I do not know your mistakes, your name, your surname, your schooling, your financial conditions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;However, I direct this letter to any resident of Blumenau and neighboring towns, who may receive light by reading this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Daniell, a very flawed servant, I write this after contending and inclining to desires.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I saw a wind like never before in Blumenau, dragging leaves and making a loud sound.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I had thought of throwing this letter from a high place, but I was told that this is not necessary, and I have to write the letters without thinking of other things.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-2&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 2&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am perplexed about today&#39;s Christianity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only talk about prosperity, victory, achievements, a fabulous life gifted, superb, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They teach people to be like the foolish;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Of whom the Bible briefly referred, as also predicted what is happening today, in 2 Timothy 4: 3:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;For the time will come when they will not endure sound doctrine, but with their ears itching, they will heap doctors for themselves according to their own lusts.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Who are these doctors? Pastors who preach prosperity today.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And many churches do not want to admit losing believers to other churches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;(competitors, as if it were a capital competition) and then they preach only what pleases man, and so they fill their churches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But we can not speak pleasing man, but speaking what is fitting for building up people and souls to please God.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 Corinthians 4:14: &amp;ldquo;I do not write these things to put you to shame, but I admonish you as my beloved children.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If I have a son that hinders him;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I will allow him to do this within my house so that while he, alive, does not come out of it,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Or with love will I rebuke him, lest he come out dead?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is similar to that which happens in the churches today.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do they prefer that the faithful keep their souls dying, or that they hear the truth even if they want to leave?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What&#39;s the use of having the church full of lost souls?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For the church with only seven saved members is better than a church with a thousand confused members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As it is written, many shall be called, but few shall be chosen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And: the door is narrow.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Galatians 1: 9-10: &amp;ldquo;Now as I told you again, now I say unto you again, If any man shall preach any other gospel unto you than that which ye have received, let it be appart: for I persuade men now or to God? Or do I seek to please men? If I were still pleasing men, I would not be a servant of Christ. &amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-3&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 3&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Today is taught to crucify, not to carry the cross.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Now, to have glory in heaven, must we have glory on earth?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is God unjust because the wicked are glorified on earth while the good suffer?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do Christians have to live as kings on earth?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has Christ ever returned, and here is paradise?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is here on earth heaven for the wicked and hell for the good?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But the earth is not everything, and it is not here that it will be revealed to us what we are to be.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For Earth, hell and heavens are similar, but different.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 Corinthians 15:19: &amp;ldquo;If we hope in Christ alone in this life, we are the most miserable of all men.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For the one who, knowing Christ, sins; than he who sins in his ignorance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;By those who say they love Christ, but their hearts are on the earth,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And they give priority to things that are vanity (vanity are things that are not eternal), they are like the most sinful of all.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-4&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 4&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Who sins more? The wanderer who can become a new creature, or what he says is a new creature and does not recognize his mistakes?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For whoever claims to be already converted, and sinning voluntarily,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He does not allow himself to become Spirit and truth, not word.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can he who says he has become converted convert himself without believing to have deviated from the path?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For they live as deviants but claiming to be converted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And yet they want to repress whom they call sinners!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What will we do about people like that? Teach them, admonishing with humility that comes from love,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And fight in prayers for those whom we believe may come to repentance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As for us, let us not think that God and the Bible are equal to these hypocrites, their doctrines, and their churches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Let us love above all things, loving God above all things,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Loving the neighbor more than we love, and loving us above the corruptions that this world offers;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gluttonies, drunking, smoking, sensuality, malice, envy and things similar to these.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For these are evil to the body (the temple of the Holy Spirit) and to the soul.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am neither a priest nor a pastor. I do not consider myself a worker, because of so many failures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I have no church, I have no religion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But I ask that you receive this letter as receiving it from an apostle, knowing that I am not.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May our greatest love be to Christ Jesus, so also shall we love the Father; for God is one.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And if we love Jesus, we suffer with him, and with him we shall rise in glory.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Galatians 1: 7: &amp;ldquo;Who is no other, but there are some who trouble you and want to disrupt the gospel of Christ.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Today, many churches are uneasy and scandalized;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being hypocrites on one side, disbelieving on the other.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-5&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 5&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But he who is of God knows that in himself he receives the presence of Jesus and the Spirit,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Who loves his neighbor and helps all, who seek to gather with other sincere Christians and admonish the wicked,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Who seeks knowledge of the truth and is not embarrassed by the affairs of this life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colossians 3:23: &amp;ldquo;Whatever you do, do it with all your heart, as to the Lord, and not to men.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;John 12: 42-43: &amp;ldquo;Yet many of the rulers believed in him;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But they did not confess him because of the Pharisees, lest they be expelled from the synagogue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For they loved the glory of men more than the glory of God. &amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Matthew 24:35: &amp;ldquo;Heaven and earth shall pass away, but my words shall not pass away.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Matthew 24: 38-39: &amp;ldquo;For as in the days before the flood they did eat, drink, marry, and marry, until the day that Noah entered into the ark.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And they did not perceive it, until the flood came, and brought them all, so shall also the coming of the Son of man be. &amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And why do those who say they are converted but sinners sin?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;John 9: 39-41: &amp;ldquo;And Jesus said unto him,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I have come into this world for judgment, that those who do not see may see, and those who see may be blind. &amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And the Pharisees that were with him heard it, and said unto him,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are we also blind? Jesus said to them,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If ye were blind, ye would have no sin; but as you now say, we see; therefore your sin remains. &amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Galatians 5:14: &amp;ldquo;Let the whole law be fulfilled in one word, in this: thou shalt love thy neighbor as thyself.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Romans 6:12: &amp;ldquo;Let not sin therefore reign in your mortal body, that ye should obey it in its lusts.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 Corinthians 2:17: &amp;ldquo;For we are not as many as counterfeiters of the word of God, but we speak of Christ sincerely, as of God in the presence of God.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read also Galatians 5: 17-25, and Philippians 4.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As a man, I got very tired writing this letter, but my spirit rejoices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read with love and diligence all the biblical quotations contained herein.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Grace and peace, and love, be with you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:mssdaniellmesquita@gmail.com&#34;&gt;mssdaniellmesquita@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blumenau, 03/15/18&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adults - 1st letter to the Blumenauans</title>
      <link>/en/2019/06/adults-1st-letter-to-the-blumenauans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 14:33:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/2019/06/adults-1st-letter-to-the-blumenauans/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;img/letters/blumenauans/1.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-1&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hi! I understand that it is impolite to read the letter which is for others, but this letter is for you, who found it out there after I threw it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I hope these words are very useful to you!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sorry if I disturbed your rush, but my intention is to build you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In ancient times, people had more time and did more things, and lived for more years, but in modern times people run a lot, feel that they have not produced enough and that time is lacking in every day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nowadays people have great infrastructure and medical care, but in contrast the lifestyle and industrialized foods (snacks, fast food, etc.) have reduced people&#39;s life expectancy, while &amp;ldquo;fit&amp;rdquo; foods are more expensive and considered, perhaps, by the majority as having a lower flavor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But speaking in ancient times: people were more dedicated to reading a letter they found.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They read with humility, attention, interest, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I ask that you be like this when reading this letter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When reading, you may think, &amp;ldquo;crazy!&amp;quot;, &amp;ldquo;Another one of those&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;tongue&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;liar&amp;rdquo;, but read it with much love.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chapter-2&#34;&gt;CHAPTER 2&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Love and faith are gratuitous, and are the greatest things that exist in the Universe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Love is the greatest gift of beings, and faith is the greatest mover on earth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What about wisdom? Proverbs 4: 7: &amp;ldquo;Wisdom is the chief thing: get wisdom, use all that you possess in gaining understanding.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And if all you have is faith?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is in faith that you can acquire wisdom.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;James 1: 5: &amp;ldquo;And if any of you lacks wisdom, let him ask of God, who giveth to all men liberally, and casteth him not, and it shall be given him.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If wisdom is the main thing, do I mistake in saying that faith is the greatest mover?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No, for with faith one acquires the chief thing called Wisdom, so faith is also chief, all of these being important in their functions, as members of a body.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 Corinthians 11:11: &amp;ldquo;Neither is a man without the woman, nor the woman without the man, in the Lord.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 Corinthians 11:12: &amp;ldquo;For as the woman is of the man, so also the man is of the woman: but all things are of God.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 Corinthians 12: 20-21: &amp;ldquo;Therefore there are many members, but one body: and the eye can not say by the hand, I have no need of thee, neither yet head to my feet: I have no need of you &amp;ldquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thinking of a weaker member, and if that is your faith?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If your faith is small? Matthew 17:20: &amp;ldquo;And Jesus saith unto them, Because of your low faith: for verily I say unto you, If ye have faith as a grain of mustard seed, ye shall say unto this mountain: pass over thither, and pass over; nothing will be impossible for you. &amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not read this with debauchery, for obviously even though your faith is a giant, you can not move a hill, for it is not God&#39;s will.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 John 5:14, &amp;ldquo;And this is the confidence which we have in him, that if we ask anything according to his will, he heareth us.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What if you ask for something that is not God&#39;s will? James 4: 3: &amp;ldquo;Ye ask, and receive not, because ye ask evilly, that ye may spend it in your pleasures.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Did you ask for a good thing and not receive it? Do not think that you asked badly, nor give up; insist, for in the time of God he does for you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jesus said in Luke 18: 7, &amp;ldquo;Shall not God execute judgment upon his elect, who cry unto him day and night, though he tarry with them?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read Matthew 17:20 again in this same letter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is your faith small, the size of a mustard seed? Matthew 13: 31-32: &amp;ldquo;And he spake another parable unto them, saying, The kingdom of heaven is like unto the grain of mustard seed, which a man hath taken in him, sowing in his field: which is the least of all the seeds; but it is the greatest of plants, and a tree is made, so that the birds of the air come and nest in their branches. &amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For if your faith is small, but you have faith!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And your faith can be exercised to grow much more, even in faith you may ask for more faith.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:mssdaniellmesquita@gmail.com&#34;&gt;mssdaniellmesquita@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
